careers.org 2019-12-14

# Careers.org | Career Resources, Career Guide, Online Education and Degree Directory

**Please Read This Privacy Statement Agreement Carefully Before Accessing Website.**  
This document was last updated effective as of May 25, 2018.

Careers.org (“CAREERS”) and our affiliated companies worldwide are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any information you share with us by using our web sites, products and services. CAREERS reserves the right to append or otherwise modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please periodically re-visit and review this page to ensure ongoing familiarity with the most current version of our Privacy Statement.

Please read this Privacy Statement carefully since by accessing our website (the “Site”) and sharing information with us, you agree to be bound by our Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Privacy Statement.

To proceed on our Site, you have been asked to provide clear and express consent to the collection, processing, and sharing of your user information via cookies and similar technologies. 

To EU Individuals: this Privacy Statement and the stated guidelines are intended to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 (the “General Data Protection Regulation” or “GDPR”) and to provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your user information in accordance with the GDPR.

If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this Site. CAREERS have established the following Privacy Statement so that you can understand the care with which we intend to treat your information. This policy describes the overall privacy practices of CAREERS regarding information we collect on our network of web sites and through our other Internet advertising mediums, including but not limited to email. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that CAREERS does not own or control, or to people that CAREERS does not employ.

**Information Collected by CAREERS: Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

CAREERS collects various types of information from you to better meet your needs and to provide you with a more relevant user experience. Some of this information is collected automatically through cookies (a small text file placed on your computer) or other Internet tracking technologies such as a tracking pixel. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. Please note that rejecting cookies by changing your browser settings may result in a lower quality experience for you while you are visiting our Site.

**Information Collected Automatically**

The types of information your browser or internet session automatically sends us each time you visit one of our sites, which we automatically collect from our web server logs, includes:

  * Your browser, e.g., Internet Explorer, Firefox, Safari, Google Chrome, UC Browser, Opera, Edge.
  * Your Internet domain, e.g., AOL, Netcom, Earthlink, etc.
  * Your computer’s operating system, e.g., Windows, Mac OS X, UNIX, Linux, iOS, Android.
  * Your navigation path, i.e., the URLs of where you come to our Site from, which of our pages you visit, and where you go as you leave.
  * Your IP Address

This information lets us see how users are finding our Site, and it tells us which pages are visited the most often so we can make our Site more useful. The non-personally identifiable information that CAREERS collects is used for marketing and sales efforts to better target advertisements and other content in an effort to create a more personally relevant experience. The information is also used to predict responses to advertisements, and to help determine which ads perform best and which content is most appropriate for different users. We may share with third parties non-personally identifiable aggregate information, such as how many individuals clicked on a specific advertisement on an anonymous or non-identifiable basis.

We participate in a cookie-based exchange. Although the exchange uses some anonymous information about you to display ads, we don’t permit these companies to collect any personal information about you. Our partners use cookies to collect anonymous information, which may be used to tailor the advertising you see on the sites or elsewhere on the web.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

**Personally Identifiable Information**

We only collect personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis. Please be cautious in determining which information (especially personally identifiable information) you choose to provide. Personal information may include name, email address, physical address, telephone or facsimile number or demographic information such as age, gender and personal interests. Once this information that you voluntarily provide is collected, it is then forwarded to the applicable entity (for example, an educational institution to which you requested information). In the context of education, upon the school(s)’ receipt of your information, an admissions representative may contact you via telephone, email or direct mail to assist with your request. Additionally, a representative from CAREERS or a third party may use your personally identifiable information that you provided to subsequently contact you by telephone in order to confirm your interest and assist you in the process, as well as to obtain your feedback on the quality of the follow-up you received and/or discuss additional education related opportunities.

The personal information you provide to us may also be used and/or combined with aggregated information and information from third parties for such purposes, including without limitation, to: (i) improve the Site’s features and functionality; (ii) provide a more personalized experience by customizing the content, products, events and services offered by us or third parties; (iii) provide information, communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; (iv) conduct research about your Site use through voluntary surveys; and (v) “pre-populate” forms. If we combine other information with personal information, we will treat the combined information as personal information under this Privacy Policy.

Your information may also be shared with our subsidiaries, affiliates or other third parties who assist us in administering the Site, including processing personal information, and various programs and promotions on our behalf. These individuals and entities can only use the information to administer our Site and programs and are bound to keep and process your information in compliance with this Statement and other confidentiality and security provisions. In addition, there is also the possibility that CAREERS, or part(s) of the company, may in the future be purchased by, or merged with, another company. In the event of such transaction, the acquiring (or merging) company will have access to all collected personally identifiable information, which will then be subject to that party’s privacy policy. CAREERS may also disclose such information to a third party if we believe, in our discretion, that we are required to do so pursuant to a subpoena, court order, or other form of legal process, to comply with requests from law enforcement agencies or a government agency, department, or body, whether or not pursuant to any form of legal process, or to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of CAREERS or of its employees. This also includes sharing information with other parties to detect or prevent the occurrence of fraud.

**Newsletters** **, Email, Promotions and/or Offers**

In some cases, we may use your personally identifiable information to provide information to you, such as to send newsletters, email, promotions and/or offers that you request, or to personalize the Site in accordance with your requests. We will provide you with directions in all emails, newsletters and/or offers on how to be removed from our lists. Please see the “Updating Information and Opting Out” section.

These communications may include notifications of activity by topic or contributor to the e-mail address that you provide to us. They are provided only to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive them as part of their user profile.

From time to time we may also provide e-mails highlighting new features, promotions or contests on the website to those users who have expressly provided us with their permission to send such communications as part of their user profile.

**To Provide Communications from Third Parties**

We respect the privacy of our users and will not disclose or distribute our user list to any third party, nor will we permit anyone else to do so. However, we may make available for rental our list of those registrants who have expressly provided us with their permission to receive third party offers as part of their user profile. In those cases, your e-mail address will be transferred to the third party. You can remove your consent to this use or modify your related user information by contacting CAREERS as indicated below.

**Third Party Advertisers and Sites**

Please also note that our Site may include third party advertising and our advertisers may contract with third-party companies such as advertising networks to serve ads on their behalf. In addition, this Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by CAREERS. These companies may also use cookies or other measures to collect both your personal and non-personally identifiable information. The information practices and privacy policies of these companies collecting data on our Site or on websites linked to CAREERS are not covered by this Privacy Statement. This Privacy Statement applies only to information collected by this Site.

**Security**

We take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the information you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. All personally identifiable information you provide is maintained in confidence by CAREERS and is not available to the public. Please note, however, that while we strive to protect your data, it may be possible for third parties not under the control of CAREERS to unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of information you transmit to us. You acknowledge and assume this risk when communicating with us.

**Videos, Bulletin Boards and Chat Rooms**

Please note that any videos that you upload and any other communication that you have through the Site is available to anyone with internet access. Please be cautious in determining which information (especially personally identifiable information) you choose to post. Any videos that you submit to CAREERS are available to the public and may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels. Please also note that if you post a message or comment on this Site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these sections, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Updating Information and Opting Out**

You may choose whether or not to provide personally identifiable information to our Site. If you choose to provide such information to CAREERS, you have the right to update your information for accuracy as well as to tell us not to make some of the uses of such information described herein or to have such information deleted in its entirety. You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time.

We will retain your information for the period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection. You may request to review, correct, delete, or otherwise modify any of the personal identifiable information that you have previously provided to us. You can do the following at any time by contacting us as provided in the “Contacting Us” section below: (i) see what information we have about you, if any; (ii) change/correct any information we have about you; (iii) have us delete any information we have about you; and (iv) inquire about our use of your information.

If you contact us, for example, to make a change in information or preferences, please provide the service for which information was provided, your full name, mailing address, phone number and email address so that we may identify you in the process, as applicable.

Requests concerning your personally identifiable information will be addressed within a reasonable timeframe. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

**Children’s Privacy**

In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), CAREERS products and services are not developed or structured to attract children. Accordingly, CAREERS will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13.

**Information on the Site**

While CAREERS uses reasonable efforts to include current and accurate information on the Site, CAREERS makes no warranties or representations as to its accuracy. CAREERS assume no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of the Site. Further, CAREERS takes no responsibility for any communications, including, messages and comments, that are posted by visitors for each other or for view by the general public. Information that is available and/or obtained in this type of forum may not be reliable. Further, CAREERS assumes no liability for the accuracy of such information and no liability for such communications arising under the laws of copyright, libel, privacy, obscenity, or otherwise.

**Changes to the Privacy Statement**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please review it frequently. In the event of a Privacy Statement change, we will revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy Statement page and will post a link to the new Privacy Statement on the home page. The new Privacy Statement will be automatically effective after it is posted and your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Statement and any updates.

**Contacting Us**

For more information, or if you have questions or concerns regarding CAREERS’ Privacy Statement, you may email or contact us at: Privacy, Careers.org, 12052 Coyne Street, Los Angeles, CA 90049 or <http://careers.org/contact-us>. Thank you for visiting our Site. We hope you have a pleasant experience while you are on the Site.
